≪(小町)ねえ
(比企谷)うん？
Hey...
(小町)なんかあった？
Did something happen?
なんもねえよ
むしろアレだな
No, nothing.
In fact, I'd say there's actually too much nothing happening in my life.
逆に俺の人生
なんもなさすぎるまである
人間万事塞翁が馬っつーけど
They say "inscrutable are the ways of Heaven,"
多少なんかあったほうが
うまくいくのかもしれんな
but maybe things go better when there's a little something going on.
What happened, Onii-chan?
どうしたの？ お兄ちゃん
いや まあ なんだ？
Oh, well, you know...
なんもねえってことだよ
That just means nothing happened.
ねえ 知ってる？
なに 豆しば？
Hey, did you know?
What's this, Mameshiba?
You always say all that hopeless stuff,
お兄ちゃんは普段から
どうしようもないこと言うけど➡
but when you're down, you sound even more hopeless.
調子悪いときは さらに
どうしようもないこと言うんだよ
ああ そう
Oh, do I?
あのさ
うん？
Listen...
結衣さんと雪乃さんと
なにかあった？
Did something happen with Yui-san and Yukino-san?
あいつらが
なにか言ってたのか？
Did they say something?
It's just what I thought.
ただ小町が
そう思っただけだよ
I see.
そっか
So? What did you do?
そいでさ なにやらかしたの？
俺が なんかやったっつー前提が
おかしいだろ
Why do you just assume that I did something?
Well, you might have done something without realizing it, right?
お兄ちゃんに自覚はなくても
なにかやってる可能性は
あるでしょうに
Oh, fine. Tell me every detail, okay?
仕方ない 一つ一つ 話してみそ
What do I say to that?
そう言われてもな
やっぱ なんもねえな
≪(小町)またまた～
Nope, nothing happened.
What, again with that?
So what happened?
で なにがあったの？
You're getting pushy. Give it a rest.
しつけえよ
いい加減にしろ
なに その言い方
Why'd you have to say it like that?
What did I say that wasn't normal?
別に普通のこと言っただけだろ
実際 しつこかったし
ウザかった
You were being pushy, and it was annoying me.
ふ～ん そう➡
I see.
じゃあ もういい 聞かない
Fine. I won't ask anymore.
そうしてくれ
Good. Don't.
(小町の足音)
小町 先 行くから
鍵かけといて
I'm leaving now. Remember to lock the door.
ああ
Sure.
(強くドアが閉まる)
≪(小町)やっぱ
なんかあったんじゃん
Something totally happened!
(小町が小走りする足音)
♬～
おはよ～
≪(女生徒)おはよ～
Morning!
Morning.
<変わらないことを>
A world that wants nothing to change... that wants stagnation, huh?
<停滞することを望んだ世界 か…>
Morning, Hachiman.
(戸塚)おはよう 八幡 エヘヘッ
Oh, morning.
ああ おはよう
あ…
どうした？
ああ いや
What is it?
Ah, nothing...
なんか普通に挨拶だなって
I just thought that was a pretty normal greeting.
ああ まあ そうだな
Oh... Well, yeah.
普通だ
That's normal.
(結衣)あ…
苦え…
Bitter...
(ため息)
(結衣の笑い声)
そんでさ 駅前のｸﾚｰﾌﾟ屋さんがね
超おいしいんだよ
Yeah, and that crêpe place by the station is so good!
≪(雪乃)そう
ゆきのん 一緒に行こう！
Is it?
Let's go there together, Yukinon!
チョコバナナが…
The choco-banana is be—
あッ…
来たのね
ああ まあな
So you're here.
Yeah, I guess.
あッ そういえば
みんな 普通だったね
Come to think of it, everyone seemed pretty normal, huh?
その えっと みんな…
I mean, uh... Everyone...
そうだな
あッ
Yeah.
見てる限りじゃ
なんともなさそうだったな
Nothing seemed out of place as far as I could see.
そう ならいいのだけれど
Really? That's good, then.
いや～ 結構
ヒヤヒヤしてたんだけど
Man, I was pretty nervous,
私が心配することじゃなかったな
みたいな
but now it's like I shouldn't have been worried.
みんな 全然 普通で…
They're all... totally normal...
I don't know what you're thinking anymore.
なに考えてるのか
よく分かんなくなっちゃった
We could never tell what he was thinking in the first place.
元々 なにを考えているかなんて
私達には分からないわ
お互いを知っていたとしても
Even if we know each other,
理解できるかは
また別の問題だもの
understanding each other is another matter.
まあ あんまり気にしてもアレだ
Well, no point in worrying about it.
俺達も普通にしてやるのが
一番じゃねえの？
Isn't it best for us to just be normal?
私達も普通に… うん
We should be normal, too...
Yeah...
普通… ね
Normal, huh?
そう それが
あなたにとっての普通なのね
So that's what's normal for you, is it?
変わらないと そう言うのね
To not change, right?
あなたは…
You're...
その…
ゆきのん！
Uh...
Yukinon!
あッ あの… あのさ
H-Hey... You know...
(ノック)
(平塚)邪魔するぞ
I'm coming in.
少し頼みたいことがあるんだが
I want to ask you guys a favor.
うん？ なにかあったのかね
Did something happen?
いや なにも
それより なんか用ですか？
No, nothing. Did you need something?
Yeah. You can come in.
ああ 入ってきていいぞ
I wanted to ask for your help.
(めぐり)ちょっと
相談したいことがあって
Shiromeguri-senpai...
城廻先輩…
あッ いろはちゃん
Iroha-chan!
Yui-senpai! Hi!
(いろは)結衣先輩 こんにちは
Yahello! It's been ages!
やっはろー 久しぶり
あッ…
生徒会長選挙の候補者？
You're running for student council president?
はい
Yeah.
あッ 今 向いてなさそうとか
思いませんでした？
You just thought I don't seem cut out for that, didn't you?
あッ いや 別に…
Uh, no, not really.
よく言われるから
分かるんですよ
I get that all the time, so I can tell!
トロそうとか 鈍そうとか
That I seem slow, or dumb...
So, is there a problem?
それで なにか問題が？
一色さんは 生徒会長に
立候補してるんだけど
Isshiki-san is running for student council president,
その… なんて言うのかな
but, well... how to put it...
We want to make sure she's not elected.
当選しないようにしたいの
あッ… えっと つまり生徒会長を
やりたくないってこと？
Um... Then you don't want to be the student council president?
≪(いろは)ああ はい そうです
Yes, that's right.
Then why are you running?
なら なぜ立候補を？
Well, I didn't volunteer myself.
えっと 私が自分で
立候補したんじゃなくて
勝手にされてて～
Someone else put me in the running.
<なにそれ どこのアイドル？>
Wait, what is this? What idol are you?
I guess you could say I stand out, in a bad way?
私 結構
悪目立ちっていうんですか…
She does seem like the type that other girls would despise, though.
<しかし アレだな こいつ
ホントに女子に嫌われそう>
I'm the soccer team manager,
and I'm friends with Hayama-senpai,
<中学にもいたなあ そりゃもう>
I knew girls like that in middle school...
so I guess that's how people see me now...
Girls who'd play guys like some kind of juggler.
<ジャグラーばりに
男子を手玉に取りまくりだった>
A lot of people say I'd be great in the role.
That's rather elaborate for a prank.
いたずらにしても
ずいぶん手が込んでますね
立候補には 30人以上の推薦人が
必要だったと思いますが
I believe you need at least 30 supporters in order to run.
そんなに？ よく集めたね
That much? I'm impressed they found so many.
無論 しでかした生徒は
こちらで指導する
I'll give the student who did it a talking-to, of course.
やりたくないなら
選挙で落ちればいい
If you don't want to do it, just lose the vote.
というか それしかないだろ
Actually, isn't that the only way?
Yeah, but the thing is, Isshiki-san is the only candidate...
う～ん ただ
立候補が一色さんだけだから
So it's a vote of confidence, then.
となると 信任投票ですね
It'd look really pathetic to lose in a vote of confidence!
信任投票で落選って
超カッコ悪いじゃないですか
あッ 応援演説をやるヤツは
決まってるのか？
Do you have someone in mind to give your campaign speech?
いえ
なら簡単で手っとり早い
No.
Then this'll be quick and easy.
Uh... What do you mean?
えっと どういうこと？
最悪 信任投票になっても
確実に落選できて
Even if it ends up a vote of confidence, we just need to make sure
一色は ﾉｰﾀﾞﾒｰｼﾞで切り抜けられれば
いいってことなんじゃねえの？
she can definitely lose without taking any damage, right?
In short, everyone just
要は 一色が原因で
落選したわけじゃないってことを
needs to understand that it's not Isshiki's fault she lost.
みんなが分かってりゃいい
そんなこと できるの？
Can we do that?
If people lose confidence in her because of her campaign speech,
応援演説が原因で
不信任になるなら
誰も一色のことは
気にしないだろ
no one will give Isshiki a second thought.
あッ…
ねえ その演説ってさ
So, who's going to give that speech?
誰がやるのかな…
そういうの ヤダな
それは…
I don't want to do that.
Well,
できるヤツがやれば
いいんじゃねえの？
we just need someone who can do it, right?
I can't approve of going about it that way.
そのやり方を
認めるわけにはいかないわ
理由は？
それは
Your reason being?
Because...
確実性がないからよ
It's too uncertain.
And a speech that breaks confidence in Isshiki-san
それに 不信任になるような
ひどい演説は
一色さんにも迷惑がかかるわ
would cause problems for her.
仮に不信任になったとしても
And even if it worked,
再選挙なんて
わざわざすると思う？
do you think they'd have a second election?
And...
それから…
生徒会への関心が低いのだから
There's not much interest in the student council,
so if they just announce the results without giving the numbers,
票数を公開せず 結果だけ出しても
誰も気にしないわ
no one will care.
つまり
その気になれば いくらでも…
That means if they wanted to, they could...
雪ノ下
Yukinoshita.
失言でした 撤回します
I shouldn't have said that. I take it back.
The only way is to back another candidate
他の候補を擁立し 選挙で勝つしか
方法はないでしょうね
and have them win the election.
そんな やる気のある人間なら
If there's anyone willing to do that,
もう立候補してないと
おかしいだろ
wouldn't they already be in the running by now?
でも やってくれそうな人に
当たってみれば…
But, I mean...
If we try asking some people who might do it...
すぐに結論は出なそうだな
また後日にしよう
Looks like this one won't be solved right away.
Let's try another day.
≪(めぐり)はい
Okay.
平塚先生
うん？
Hiratsuka-sensei.
少しよろしいでしょうか
うん？
Do you have a moment?
今のところ
勝敗はどうなっていますか？
What are the standings right now?
Huh?
あッ？
勝敗って？
Standings?
誰が一番 人に奉仕できるか
A showdown to see who can do the most service,
人の悩みを
解決できるかって勝負だ
and solve the most people's problems.
はあ？
勝ったら なんでも
The winner can order the loser to do anything.
言うことを聞いてもらえる
そんなのあったんだ
We were doing that?
R-Right...
そッ そうだな
Well, you did work together on several of those cases...
まあ 協力して
事に当たる場合が多かったからな
I think you're all coming along well. Yep.
みんな
よくやってる感じだな うん！
(平塚のため息)
３人の相対的な評価であれば
If you want a relative assessment of the three of you,
私の独断と偏見で
下すことができるが
I can give you one from my own biased perspective.
それで構いません
That would be fine.
If I'm just evaluating your results alone,
単純な結果だけを
評価するのであれば➡
比企谷が一歩勝る➡
Hikigaya's a step ahead.
もっとも 過程や事後の経過を
考慮に入れると➡
But if I consider your methods and follow-ups,
Yukinoshita's faring better.
雪ノ下のほうがよかろう
ともあれ いずれにしても➡
But either way,
由比ヶ浜の貢献なくしては
成り立たないものではあるが…
you'd never get anywhere without Yuigahama's contributions.
So you're saying there is no winner yet?
つまり 勝負は まだついてないと
That's what I'm saying.
そういうことになる
Then even if our opinions are divided, it won't be a problem, correct?
なら 私達の意見が割れても
なんら問題ない
ということになりますね
えッ どういうこと？
Huh? What do you mean?
私と彼が 同じやり方をとる必要は
ないということよ
I mean he and I don't have to use the same method.
ああ…
まあ そうだな
Yeah, true.
No point in working together against our will.
お互い 無理して合わせたって
意味ないしな
So what's the club going to do until you reach a solution?
それで 解決するまで
部活はどうするかね？
自由参加でよいかと
I suggest free participation.
I guess that's reasonable.
≪(平塚)まあ 妥当なところか
ああ…
なれ合いなんて 私もあなたも
一番嫌うものだったのにね
And I thought that kind
of deception was what you and I both hated most.
≪(平塚)なにかあったのかね？
Did something happen?
なにも
そうか
Why?
I see.
まあいい 君は優しいからな➡
Never mind.
You're such a nice kid...
I know you've helped a lot of people.
救われた人間だって少なくない
いや そういうことは…
That's not...
私は こう見えて
結構 えこひいきするんだ
Despite appearances, there are certain people I'm partial to.
Is that acceptable for a teacher?
それ 教師として
どうなんですか？
I believe in helping people grow through praise.
褒めて伸ばす方針でね
とても そうは思えませんけどね
I wouldn't have thought so.
その分 叱りもするからな
But I give just as much discipline, too.
With the way you do things,
君のやり方では 本当に助けたい
誰かに出会ったとき
when you meet someone you really want to help,
助けることができないよ
you won't be able to.
To:
Subject :
New message
Komachi
Inbox
Totsuka Saika
Saika here
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
Hey, there's a face I don't see often.
(陽乃)おや 珍しい顔だ ウッフフ
あッ…
別に逃げることないじゃない
There was no need to run away, you know.
失礼だなあ
Talk about rude.
比企谷君
はい
Hikigaya-kun...
Yes?
Tell me something interesting.
なんか面白い話して
その超嫌そうなリアクション
That super disgusted reaction!
いや～ 期待どおりだな
Yeah, it's everything I expected!
ねえ 雪乃ちゃんは元気？
Hey, how's Yukino-chan doing?
Well, same as ever, I guess.
まあ 普段と変わらずですかね
Yeah? Glad to hear it.
≪(陽乃)そっか なら よかった
And? Have there been any developments?
それで
少しは進展があったのかね？
はあ…
修学旅行あったんじゃないの？
Huh?
Didn't you have a field trip?
よく知ってますね
うちに お土産 届いたから
You know about that, huh?
She sent souvenirs home.
She had them delivered?
わざわざ宅配便を…
顔を合わせたくなかったんでしょ
She probably didn't want to see us.
なのに お土産は買っていくのか
Yet she bought souvenirs for you?
律儀だな
ああ
Dutiful of her.
Oh, I don't think that's it.
そういうのじゃないと思うよ
嫌いだけど
嫌われたくはないのよね
She hates us, but she doesn't want us to hate her.
でも もう大きな行事もなくなるし
But there won't be any more big events at school,
あとは受験に集中って感じかな
so I guess the rest will be preparing for exams, huh?
退屈なんじゃない？
別に そうでも
Won't you be bored?
Not particularly.
生徒会選挙とか
まだ なんやかんやありますし
There's still the student council election and other stuff.
あッ そっか
めぐりも ようやく引退だね
Oh, yeah.
Meguri'll finally have to retire.
Knowing Meguri, I bet
どうせ めぐりのことだから
she asked Yukino-chan to be the next president, didn't she?
雪乃ちゃんに 生徒会長やってくれ
って頼んだんじゃないの？
No, actually, she didn't.
ああ いや
そういうことはなかったですね
No? How boring.
な～んだ つまんないの
じゃあ 雪乃ちゃんは
So Yukino-chan won't be student council president, then.
生徒会長やらないんだ
でしょうね
Guess not.
ふ～ん
あの それがなにか？
Um, is that a problem?
うん？ いや
私は やらなかったからさ
Oh, no, it's just that I wasn't president.
はあ… つまんないなあ
How boring...
≪(折本)あれ 比企谷？➡
Huh? Hikigaya?
Whoa! This totally takes me back!
うわッ 超ナツいんだけど
レアキャラじゃない？
It's rare to see you!
折本…
Orimoto...
<中学の同級生なんて
記憶の奥底で>
I thought all my middle school classmates
had been discarded into the deepest corner of my memory...
<打ち捨てられてるものだとばかり
思っていたのに>
<折本かおりの名前は
すんなりと出てきてしまった>
And now Orimoto Kaori's name pops up, just like that.
あれ 比企谷って総武高なの？
あッ ああ…
Hey, Hikigaya, you go to Soubu High?
Y-Yeah.
へえ～ 頭良かったんだ
知らなかった
Oh, you must be smart, then! I had no idea!
You never talked to anyone, after all.
比企谷
全然 人と話してなかったもんね
あッ… 彼女さん？
Your girlfriend?
No.
いや
だよね 絶対ないと思った
Yeah, I thought not! No way!
<なに愛想笑いしてんだ 俺は
気持ち悪い>
Why am I forcing myself to laugh? Creepy...
Could it be this is a friend of yours, Hikigaya-kun?
もしかして 比企谷君のお友達？
<その聞き方だと
｢友達いたの？｣に聞こえるのは>
When you say it like that,
is it my imagination or does it sound like "You have a friend?" Is it?
<気のせいですか そうですか>
She was in my class in middle school.
中学の同級生です
折本かおりです
I'm Orimoto Kaori.
ふ～ん…
ああ 私は雪ノ下陽乃ね
Oh, I'm Yukinoshita Haruno, Hikigaya-kun's...
比企谷君の… ねえ
うん？
Hey...
私って 比企谷君のなんなの？
いや 俺に聞かれても
What am I to you?
Uh, don't ask me...
友達っていうのは変だよね➡
It'd be weird to say I'm a friend...
ああ お姉さんとか…
An older sister?
その間をとって
彼女っていうのはどう？
Why don't we take the middle ground and say I'm your girlfriend?
普通に 学校の先輩ってことで
いいんじゃないですか？
Can't we just say you're an alumna from my high school?
Aw, you're no fun.
つれないな～➡
しっかし 比企谷君と同じ中学か
なんか面白いことなかったの？
Anyway, you went to middle school with him, huh?
Got any interesting stories?
≪(折本)ええ～？
Uh...
Oh, like love stories!
コイバナ！ お姉さん
比企谷君のコイバナ 聞きたいな
I wanna hear about Hikigaya-kun's love life!
あッ そういえば 私
比企谷に告られたりしたんですよ
Actually, Hikigaya asked me out once.
(仲町)ウソ～
No way!
それ気になるな
That makes me curious!
He had never even talked to me before, so it was a total shock!
≪(折本)それまで全然 話したこと
なかったから 超ビビって
I talked to you. I e-mailed you, too.
<話したことはある
メールだってした>
<お情けでも 哀れみでも
交換してもらったアドレスに>
To the address you gave me out of either sympathy or pity.
<どうでもいい理由をこじつけては
メールをし>
I made up the dumbest reasons to e-mail you,
<返ってくるか否かに 一喜一憂し
そんなことがあったことも>
then bounced between excited and depressed, waiting to see if you'd respond.
Orimoto has no idea that happened,
and probably doesn't even remember.
<折本は知らないし
覚えてもいないんだろう…>
≪(陽乃)へえ～
比企谷君が告白ねえ
Wow, Hikigaya-kun asked a girl out, huh?
まあ 昔のことなんで…
Well, it was a long time ago...
Yeah, it was ages ago, so it doesn't really matter, huh?
だよね～
昔のことだし 別にいいよね➡
あッ そうだ 総武高なら
葉山君って知ってる？
Oh, hey! If you're at Soubu High, do you know Hayama-kun?
あッ… ああ まあ一応
Yeah, you could say that.
Seriously?!
マジ？ ほら 千佳
葉山君 紹介してもらえるかもよ
Hear that, Chika? He could introduce you to Hayama-kun!
ええ～？ 私はいいよ
Oh, that's not necessary...
いや 知り合いじゃないし
Well, he's not a friend or anything.
Oh, yeah, I can't see you having any connection with him.
ああ～ だよね 接点なさそう
ハハハ…
≪(陽乃)ふ～ん 面白そう
Hmm... This sounds fun.
は～い お姉さん 紹介しちゃうぞ
Okay! I'll introduce you!
はあ？
Huh?
(呼び出し中)
Hey, Hayato? Can you come out right now?
ああ 隼人 今すぐ来れる？
ていうか 来て➡
In fact, just come.
場所は駅近のﾄﾞｰﾅﾂｼｮｯﾌﾟ
あんた 何してんすか…
We're in the donut place by the station.
What are you doing?
ウッフフ
Bye, Hayama-kun!
葉山君 またね～
メールするね
We'll e-mail you!
Oh my God!
≪(折本)ヤバイ！
≪(仲町)カッコよかった
He's so hot!
(葉山)どうして こんなまねを？
Why'd you do this?
だって面白そうだし
また それか
Well, it seemed like fun.
That again?
で なぜ彼まで ここに？
関係なさそうだけど
And why is he here?
He didn't have anything to do with it.
≪(陽乃)そんなことないよ
Not true at all.
That girl with the perm is the girl Hikigaya-kun used to like!
あのパーマの子ね 比企谷君が
昔 好きだった子なんだって➡
雪乃ちゃんが知ったら
どんな顔するかなあ
I wonder how Yukino-chan would react if she knew...
Well, that was great for killing some time.
うん いい感じに時間もつぶれた
じゃ 私は もう行くね
I'm gonna take off now.
比企谷君
つきあってくれて ありがと
Thanks for keeping me company, Hikigaya-kun.
Bye!
じゃあね
(比企谷のため息)
君は 陽乃さんに
好かれているんだな
Haruno-san really likes you.
はあ？ アホか
あれは からかってるだけだろ
Huh? Are you nuts? She's just tormenting me.
あの人は 興味のないものには
ちょっかい出したりしないよ
She doesn't mess with people she's not interested in.
なにもしないんだ
好きなものを構いすぎて殺すか➡
She doesn't do anything.
She either kills people she likes with too much attention
嫌いなものを
徹底的につぶすことしかしない
or thoroughly crushes people she doesn't like.
そりゃ怖い
How scary.
あッ… おッ おはよう
M-Morning!
ああ
Hey.
今日ってさ 部室 行く？
Are you coming to the club room today?
いや 行かない
No, I'm not.
だッ だよね…
Y-Yeah, I guess not...
あの… いろはちゃんと もう少し
話してみようってことでさ
Listen, we decided to talk with Iroha-chan a little more.
Like, we were hoping to figure out some plan...
その… なにか方針 固めよう
みたいな
And... It didn't feel right not to let you know, so...
それで ヒッキーが知らないまま
っていうのも ちょっとアレだから
Well, if it's just to listen...
まあ 話聞くだけなら
How long has it been since I faced off with Yukinoshita one-on-one?
<雪ノ下と
正面切って対立するなんて>
<いつ以来だろうか>
It'll be the same now.
<今も同じだ 今回も俺のやり方を
雪ノ下が否定する>
Yukinoshita will reject my methods again.
<同じなら 問題はなにもない>
If it's the same, there's no problem.
(戸が開く)
Hey, you're here...
あッ 来てくれた
All right, let's begin.
では 始めましょう
とりあえず いろはちゃん以外の
候補を誰か立てて
For starters, I think it'd be best to find a candidate other than you
決選投票で穏便に負けるのが
一番いいと思うんだけど
and have you lose peacefully in the final vote.
そうですね
でも すごい人に負けるほうが➡
Yeah...
But I'd feel better if I lost to someone really amazing.
私的には いい感じです
I came up with a campaign pledge and speech for the candidate we select.
こちらが立てる候補の公約と
演説の内容は考えておいたから
お前らが公約 考えるってことは
If you guys come up with the pledge,
完全な傀儡候補なんだが…
それでいいのか？
that makes them a puppet candidate.
Is that what you want?
If that candidate wins, what happens to the student council?
もし当選したとして そのあとの
生徒会運営は どうするんだ？
だッ だから それがちゃんと
できる人を探せばいいだけで…
L-Like we said, we just have to find someone capable—
That'll just make it even harder.
なおさら ハードルが上がるぞ
あとあとのことを考えたら
If you think about what comes after,
you'll realize there's not much of a point.
大して意味ないし
あんまりいい手じゃない
It's not a very good idea.
Then what point is there in doing it your way?
なら あなたのやり方には
なんの意味があるの？
今回に限って言えば
とりあえず回避
Speaking strictly of this case,
she'd avoid being elected and lose the voters' confidence,
投票で不信任になったあと
補欠選挙については手を引いて…
then decline to run in the by-election...
今回に限って？ いえ 違う
"Speaking strictly of this case"?
No, you're not.
あなたは
前も そうやって回避したわ
You avoided the problem last time, too.
それで なんか問題あったか？
And? Was there a problem with that?
You're the one who said there's no point in something that superficial.
そんなうわべだけのものに
意味なんてないと言ったのは
あなただったはずよ
You're not changing that stance,
are you?
変える気はないのね…
ああ
No.
あッ あのさ あの…
H-Hey, um...
Um...
(比企谷がイスから立ち上がる)
そろそろ帰るわ
I'm going home.
ああ…
Silently,
Yukinoshita Yukino Makes Her Decision.
#04 And Yuigahama Yui Makes Her Declaration.
♬～
Hey!
Will this be okay?
If we find someone good, it'll make things easier for me, too, but...
It'd have to be someone like Hayama, then.
Not Hayama-senpai!
Well, if it comes to it, I'll do something.
I appreciate it!
No one else will help me.
You guys are the only ones I can count on.
Oh...
Well, I've got club.
Thanks for your help!
あの～ 大丈夫なんですかね
それなりの人が出てくると
私も気が楽で いいんですけど
そうなると 葉山クラスになるな
葉山先輩はダメです
まあ 最悪どうにかする
助かります
誰も助けてくれないんですもん
もう先輩達しか頼れないんですよ
あッ 私 部活あるので➡
では よろしくで～す